When the world feels broken and far away.
When the days turn heavy and fade to
gray. When time itself seems
lost, all's unknown. My heart is
waiting to bring you home. I'd tear the
sky
open just to see you again. I will
cross the oceans to see you back again.
I will love you deeply to erase your pain.
I will sing forever your
sweetest refrain. I will paint the heavens
with your
name. I will do everything just to see you
again.
When the stars forget their silver
glow. When the rivers stop the way
they flow. When every song has
lost its tune. I'll be the
dawn that breaks your gloom. I'll
breathe you meaning when hope is thin.
I'll arrange the sky where your sun
begins.
I'd tear the sky open just to see you
again.
I will cross the oceans to see you back
I will love you deeply to erase your pain.
I will sing forever your
sweetest refrain. I will paint the heavens
with your
name. I will do everything just to see you
again.
And if the world should fade to dust, my
heart will still
remember us. No void so vast, no night so
long,
no silence so deep, no shadow too wide can
steal the love I hold
inside. And in the last light, let it be
clear. I loved you
always loud and clear, Roses of
Rome.